<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Stud.IP</string>
    <string name="url_field">server</string>
    <string name="continue_msg">continue</string>
    <string name="username_field">username</string>
    <string name="password_field">password</string>
    <string name="login_error_title">Error</string>
    <string name="restore_error_message">An error has occurred while trying to reconnect. Check you network connectivity or try to log in again.</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_event">Courses</string>
    <string name="menu_files">Files</string>
    <string name="menu_messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome %1$s !</string>
    <string name="members_dialog_title">Participants</string>
    <string name="mkdir">New directory</string>
    <string name="upload">upload file</string>
    <string name="select_file">select file</string>
    <string name="delete">delete</string>
    <string name="dir">Directory</string>
    <string name="file">file</string>
    <string name="delete_msg">really delete?</string>
    <string name="message_subject">Subject</string>
    <string name="message_sender">Sender</string>
    <string name="message_time">time</string>
    <string name="message_new">write message</string>
    <string name="message_delete_title">delete message</string>
    <string name="message_delete_msg">Really delete this message?</string>
    <string name="message_search">Error</string>
    <string name="message_send">send</string>
    <string name="message_no_addressee">no addressee</string>
    <string name="message_no_subject">no subject</string>
    <string name="message_no_content">no content</string>
    <string name="hint_addressee">Addressee</string>
    <string name="hint_subject">Subject</string>
    <string name="hint_title">Title</string>
    <string name="hint_content">Content</string>
    <string name="forum_create">create Topic</string>


    <string name="autologout_msg">Your session has expired. Continue without a connection or log in again.</string>
    <string name="autologout_relogin">log in again</string>
    <string name="con_lost_msg">A connection to you Stud.IP server cannot be established. Continue without a connection or check your network connectivity.</string>
    <string name="con_lost_title">Connection lost</string>

    <string name="crash_msg">Unfortunately the app crashed. Please report the error and how it happened.</string>
    <string name="crash_clipboard">copy Crash-Log to clipboard</string>
    <string name="crash_mail">send Crash-Log to unofficial_studip_app_bugs@web.de</string>
    <string name="crash_github">open issue on Github</string>
    <string name="crash_restart">restart app</string>

    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_main">Settings:</string>
    <string name="clear_credentials">delete login data</string>
    <string name="clear_credentials_dialog">really delete login data?</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="settings_theme">Theme:</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_dark">dark</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_light">light</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_auto">auto</string>
    <string name="settings_notification_service">Service for background notifications.</string>
    <string name="settings_notification_service2">runy every</string>
    <string name="settings_notification_service3">minutes</string>
    <string name="settings_experimental">Experimental features can be activated here:</string>
    <string name="auth_setting">Authentication method</string>
    <string name="auth_basic">HTTP Basic Authentication</string>
    <string name="auth_basic_desc">With HTTP Basic Authentication the username and password is send with every request.\nTo secure your password, unencrypted connections are refused.\nThe username and password have to be saved on the device. They are encrypted in a file, which only the app can access, but if the operating system itself is hacked (or you rooted your device), another app could get the key from the operating system and decrypt the username and password.\nBut for normal use it should be safe enough.\nThe advantage over a session cookie is that a session cookie eventually expires and you have to log in again. Because with HTTP Basic Authentication the username and password are stored on the device, you only have to log in once (as log as you don\'t change the password).</string>
    <string name="auth_cookie">session cookie</string>
    <string name="auth_cookie_desc">This is the method browsers use. Username and password are used to fetch a session cookie, after that the password is deleted.\nOnly the cookie is saved on the device, with the same security as the password with HTTP Basic Authentication. If the cookie is leaked, someone can impersonate you for as long as the cookie lasts, but they cannot change your password.\nThe downside is that the cookie eventually expires and you have to log in again.</string>
    <string name="auth_oauth">OAuth 2</string>
    <string name="auth_oauth_desc">Not implemented yet. The safest method: It works like a session cookie, but instead of entering the username and password in the app, you are redirected to the Stud.IP-Server and have to log in there.\nThe app only gets the authentication token afterwards, which works like a session cookie.</string>
    <string name="settings_developer">Developer settings:\nThese settings could make the app unstable or lower the security. Use at your own risk.</string>
    <string name="semester_select">select semester</string>
    <string name="my_documents">Your files</string>
    <string name="not_logged_in">not logged in</string>
    <string name="message_no_search">unable to connect to server, cannot search users</string>
    <string name="message_no_send">could not send message</string>
    <string name="message_send_successfully">message send</string>
    <string name="help_button">view help</string>
    <string name="help_content"><![CDATA["<big><h1>Help</h1></big>
<h2>1. Login</h2>
First you should choose you authentication method from the settings.<br>
If you only want to log in once, you should use HTTP Basic authentication.<br>
If you don't want you username and password stored on the device (don't worry they're encrypted), you should choose the session cookie.<br>
OAuth isn't implemented yet.<br>
If you want more information about the authentication methods, long press on them in the settings screen.<br><br>
To log in you have to select you Stud.IP server.<br>
You can look for it in the list (scrolling is possible), or type it in yourself (without https://).<br>
Then you have to enter your username and password.<br>
<br><br>
<h2>2. General & Settings</h2>
All dialogs and screens use swipe-to-refresh to get new data from the server.<br>
Apart from the files all data is cached on the device and can be viewed without an internet connection.<br>
The files have to be downloaded manually on demand.<br>
The notification service can send you notifications if the data changes.<br>
You can set the update frequency and notification priority in the settings.<br>
The notification service only shows notifications you enabled in the Stud.IP notification settings.<br>
These settings can be changed in-app under "Stud.IP notification settings".<br>
With the document provider you can use your Stud.IP files like all other files on your device.<br>
After you logged in, you can use the settings screen to select the courses you wish to expose via the document provider.<br>
You can also set whether to show image previews when using mobile data.<br><br>

<h2>3. Home</h2>
On this screen you can see your Stud.IP name and the global Stud.IP news.<br><br>

<h2>4. Courses</h2>
On this screen you can view your courses for a specific semester.<br>
The icons for the courses work like on the website, but some features aren't implemented yet.<br>
You can use the flag icon to view course news.<br>
With the file icon you can view the files of a specific course.<br><br>



<h2>5. Files</h2>
On this screen you can view your files and course files.<br>
Tap \"…\" to return to the parent directory, hold to return to you own files.<br>
Tap on a folder to view its contents, tap on a file to download it.<br>
Long press on a file or folder to delete it.<br><br>

<h2>6. Messages</h2>
On this screen you can view and write Stud.IP messages.<br>
Long press on a message to delete it.<br>
To choose the addressee the app searches for known users with a name like the one you wrote.<br>
When you press the "Search" button, the app searches for new users with the specified name in the Stud.IP system.<br>
Add the addressee by tapping it in the list.<br>
Long press on an addressee to remove it.<br>
<br><br>

<h2>7. Courseware plugin</h2>
By clicking the courseware icon for a course in the courses screen you can view the Courseware, if there is any.<br>
Tap in a chapter on the left to load the subchapters, tap on a subchapter to load the sections.<br>
Supported blocks are:<br>
HTML<br>
Opencast<br>
PDF<br>
<br><br>

<h2>8. Meetings plugin</h2>
Tapping the meetings icon for a course loads all meeting rooms available.<br>
When you click a button, a new window will open with the BigBlueButton conference.<br>
Currently only works with HTTP basic auth.<br>
When navigating away, the window automatically goes into picture-in-picture mode and the presentation is set to fullscreen, so the conference can continue without interruption.<br>
As long as the conference is active, there is a non-dismissable notification present.<br>
The notification has actions to exit the conference and to toggle the microphone.<br>
Tapping the notification returns to the conference in full-screen.<br>
The PiP-window also has a button to toggle the microphone.<br>
<br><br>
"]]></string>
    <string name="view">View: %1$s</string>
    <string name="download">Download: %1$s</string>
    <string name="view_with">View with:</string>
    <string name="upload_failed">Error processing the file</string>
    <string name="settings_system">Open system settings for the app</string>
    <string name="settings_system_notification">Open system notification settings</string>
    <string name="channel_forum">Forum</string>
    <string name="channel_files">Files</string>
    <string name="channel_messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="channel_other">Other</string>
    <string name="settings_notifications">Notifications:</string>
    <string name="notification_visibility">Visibility:</string>
    <string name="notification_public">always</string>
    <string name="notification_private">only title on lockscreen</string>
    <string name="notification_secret">not on lockscreen</string>
    <string name="notification_priority">Priority:</string>
    <string name="notification_priority_desc">Priority goes from invisible on the left, without sound, with sound to heads-up notification.</string>
    <string name="own_files">Your files</string>
    <string name="document_provider">Document provider</string>
    <string name="document_provider_courses">Courses to accessible with the document provider:</string>
    <string name="document_provider_thumbnails">Show Thumbnails</string>
    <string name="document_provider_recents">Show recent documents</string>
    <string name="document_provider_search">Enable search</string>
    <string name="load_on_mobile">Load images while using mobile data</string>
    <string name="load_notification_settings">Load</string>
    <string name="save_notification_settings">Save</string>
    <string name="studip_notification_settings">Stud.IP notification settings</string>
    <string name="courses">Courses</string>
    <string name="notification_settings_error">could not set notification settings</string>
    <string name="notification_settings_success">notification settings saved</string>
    <string name="channel_meetings">Meetings</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="toggle_mic">toggle microphone</string>
    <string name="mic_on">microphone on</string>
    <string name="mic_off">microphone off</string>
    <string name="login_error_message">Error while connecting to the server. Are you connected to the internet?</string>
    <string name="login_error_auth">The username or password is wrong.</string>
    <string name="login_error_no_api"><![CDATA["The Stud.IP API is not enabled for the server. Contact your system administrator and tell them to enable the REST API. If they ask what routes need to be enabled, <a href="https://github.com/tareksander/Stud.IP-App">send them a link to the Github Readme</a>"]]></string>
    <string name="discovery_error">Could not discover available features. Assuming all Features are enabled. Some Features might not work. You can re-scan for available features in the settings screen.</string>
    <string name="discovery_title">Disabled features</string>
    <string name="feature_global_news">Global news</string>
    <string name="feature_files">File screen</string>
    <string name="feature_user_files">View user files</string>
    <string name="feature_course_files">View course files</string>
    <string name="feature_forum">Use course forums</string>
    <string name="feature_messages">Messages screen</string>
    <string name="feature_courses">Courses screen</string>
    <string name="feature_planner">Planner screen &amp; widget</string>
    <string name="feature_blubber">Blubber</string>
    <string name="discovery_msg"><![CDATA["
%1$s<br>
If you want to use these features, contact you administrator and send them a link to the <a href="https://github.com/tareksander/Stud.IP-App">Github Readme</a>, so they can enable the features.
"]]></string>
    <string name="scan_features">re-scan features</string>
    <string name="ignore_missing_features">ignore missing features</string>
    <string name="ignore_missing_features_msg">Missing features might partially work if a part of the API has been enabled, but not all that is required for a feature to fully function. The missing features might work fine, or not at all. Correct function cannot be guaranteed.</string>


</resources>